1. callTestCase(findTestCase("common_test _cases/do_sign out"), [:], CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
1. scrollToElement(findTestObject("sign_out/user_profile"), 0)
7. Click on user profile
13. Click on sign out
5. callTestCase(findTestCase("common_test _cases/login_Page"), ["headerDashboard":headerDashboard, "loginId":EA1, "Password":Password], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
3. Navigate to legal URL
9. Verify Login tab
15. Verify Login Page header
21. Enter Login id
27. Enter Password
33. Click on Login button
37. delay(7)
43. Verify after login Dashbard page opned
9. waitForPageLoad(longTime)
15. Visiable Quote Accepted tab
3. Click on Quote Accepted tab
7. scrollToPosition(0, 450)
13. Click on filter icon
19. Select Property type Commercial
25. Select Property Leasehold
31. Enter Post code
37. Verify Apply button is clickable
3. Click on Apply button
9. Verify Created Quote is available
3. Verify created Sell/ Buy quote displayed on tab
9. Verify Assigned to button is clickable
3. Click on Assigned to button
9. Verify Case Assignment is opnened
3. Verify that Case Assignment pop up title
9. Enter user name
15. Select user
21. Click on Update
27. Verify assigned Estate agent
33. Click on Created property
39. Verify Deal status page opened
3. Verify that assigned EA property opened
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())