3. Verify that Correspondence Address progress step
9. Verify Correspondence Address is visible
3. Verify header as Correspondence Address
9. Select check box Correspondence AddressSame as Buying Address
15. Unselect check box Correspondence AddressSame as Buying Address
21. Enter PostCode
25. delay(5)
31. Click on Select Address drop down
35. com.wecomplete.keywords.TestBase.clickUsingJS(findTestObject("Quote/Correspondence_Address_Page/DD_Select_Address"), shortTime)
39. delay(5)
45. Select Address from Drop down
51. Click on “Save&Next” button
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())