1. xpath = "//*[@id="" + currentDate() + ""]"
1. dateFormat = DateTimeFormatter.ofPattern("d-MMMM-yyyy")
5. now = LocalDateTime.now()
9. out.println(dateFormat.format(now))
13. return dateFormat.format(now)
5. out.println(xpath)
9. to = new com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.TestObject(objectName)
13. to.addProperty("xpath", EQUALS, xpath)
19. Click on Current date of calendar
25. Verify Reminder tab is present
3. Click on Reminder tab
9. Enter event title
15. Click on Save button
19. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Deal Status/Calendar/Reminder_Section/get_reminder"), shortTime)
25. Verify created reminder
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())
1. println(testSuiteContext.getTestSuiteId())