3. Verify Document Sign button is clickable
3. Scroll to  Document Sign button
9. Click on Document Sign button
15. Verify Document Sign pop is opened
3. Get Document Sig pop up header
9. Click on Me & others button
15. Enter Signer name or id
21. Click on Add as external button
25. directory = new java.io.File()
29. signDocument = directory.getAbsolutePath() + "\Data Files\Property Images\SignDocument.pdf"
33. out.println(signDocument)
39. Upload file
45. Click on Request Signature button
51. Verify Document signature requested successfully alter message
57. Clicon on Ok button
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())