1. callTestCase(findTestCase("common_test _cases/login_Page"), ["headerDashboard":headerDashboard, "loginId":User1, "Password":Password, "baseEAUrl":baseEAUrl], CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
3. Navigate to legal URL
9. Verify Login tab
15. Verify Login Page header
21. Enter Login id
27. Enter Password
33. Click on Login button
37. delay(7)
43. Verify after login Dashbard page opned
5. waitForPageLoad(longTime)
9. if (verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/Dashborad/hedaer_Your Recent Propertie"), shortTime) == true)
3. Your Recent Propertie header
9. Visible Quote Accepted tab
1. delay(5)
7. Click on Quote Accepted tab
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())