3. Verify that Personal Details progress step
9. Verify  Primary Contact Details header is visible
1. com.wecomplete.keywords.TestBase.isElementPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/Quote/Personal_Details_Page/header_Primary Contact Details"), shortTime)
7. Enter first name
13. Enter Last name
19. Enter email id
25. Enter mobile number
31. Click on check box make same as Joint Seller 2
37. Verify Joint seller 2 Contact Details header
43. Enter Joint holder First Name
49. Enter Joint holder Last Name
55. Enter Joint holder Phone Number
61. Enter Joint holder Email id
67. Click on “Save&Next” button
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())