1. callTestCase(findTestCase("common_test _cases/do_sign out"), [:], CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
1. scrollToElement(findTestObject("sign_out/user_profile"), shortTime)
7. Click on user profile
13. Click on sign out
5. callTestCase(findTestCase("common_test _cases/login_Page"), ["headerDashboard":headerDashboard, "loginId":EA1, "Password":Password, "baseEAUrl":baseEAUrl], CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
3. Navigate to legal URL
9. Verify Login tab
15. Verify Login Page header
21. Enter Login id
9. waitForPageLoad(longTime)
15. Visiable Quote Accepted tab
3. Click on Quote Accepted tab
9. Scroll to filter icon
15. Click on filter icon
21. Select Property type Commercial
27. Select Property Leasehold
33. Enter Post code
39. Verify Apply button is clickable
3. Click on Apply button
9. Verify Created Quote is available
3. Verify created Sell/ Buy quote displayed on tab
9. Verify Assigned to button is clickable
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())