3. Navigate to  legal URL
9. Click on Sell tab
15. Enter Sell Property details
3. Verify Quote page header
9. Verify sell Property tab is visible
3. Verify the Selling Property Details page header
9. Enter  price of Sell property
15. Enter Post code
21. Click on Enter Address Manually
27. Enter Plot/Flat/House No
33. Enter Street name
39. Select Number of seller
45. Select Property type Commercial
51. Select Property Leasehold
57. Enter Comment
63. Click on “Save&Next” button
21. Enter Personal details
3. Verify that Personal Details progress step
9. Verify  Primary Contact Details header is visible
1. com.wecomplete.keywords.TestBase.isElementPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/Quote/Personal_Details_Page/header_Primary Contact Details"), shortTime)
7. Enter first name
13. Enter Last name
19. Enter email id
25. Enter mobile number
31. Click on check box make same as Joint Seller 2
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())
1. println(testSuiteContext.getTestSuiteId())