1. callTestCase(findTestCase("common_test _cases/login_Page"), ["headerDashboard":headerDashboard, "loginId":User1, "Password":Password], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
3. Navigate to legal URL
9. Verify Login tab
15. Verify Login Page header
21. Enter Login id
27. Enter Password
33. Click on Login button
37. delay(7)
43. Verify after login Dashbard page opned
5. waitForPageLoad(longTime)
9. if (verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/Dashborad/hedaer_Your Recent Propertie"), shortTime) == true)
3. Your Recent Propertie header
9. Verify created first quote dispalyed on recent property section
15. Verify created second quote  dispalyed on recent property section
21. Visible Quote Accepted tab
1. delay(5)
7. Click on Quote Accepted tab
13. Verify created Sell/ Buy quote displayed on tab
19. Verify created Sell/ Buy quote displayed on tab
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())